<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="story_lines">
       <item>"Arthur Curry, half human half from Atlantis, goes on a trip of a lifetime.\n
		   Not only does this adventure compel him to come to terms with his real identity,\n
		   but it also forces him to discover whether he is entirely worthy of fulfilling his own destiny:\n
		   becoming a king"</item>
        <item>"In the mythical continent of Westeros,\n
            several powerful families fight for control of the Seven Kingdoms.\n
            As conflict erupts in the kingdoms of men,\n
            an ancient enemy rises once again to threaten them all.\n
            Meanwhile, the last heirs of a recently usurped dynasty plot to take back their homeland from across the Narrow Sea."</item>
        <item>"Miles Morales is a New York teen struggling with school,\n
        friends and, on top of that, being the new Spider-Man.\n
        When he comes across Peter Parker, the erstwhile saviour of New York,\n
        in the multiverse, Miles must train to become the new protector of his city."</item>
        <item>"After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War (2018),\n
            the universe is in ruins due to the efforts of the Mad Titan, Thanos.\n
            With the help of remaining allies,\n
            the Avengers must assemble once more in order to undo Thanos' actions\n
            and restore order to the universe once and for all,\n
            no matter what consequences may be in store."</item>
        <item>"Harry's fourth year at Hogwarts is about to start and he is enjoying the summer vacation with his friends.\n
            They get the tickets to The Quidditch World Cup Final but after the match is over,\n
            people dressed like Lord Voldemort's 'Death Eaters'\n
            set a fire to all the visitors' tents,\n
            coupled with the appearance of Voldemort's symbol,\n
            the 'Dark Mark' in the sky, which causes a frenzy across the magical community.\n
            That same year, Hogwarts is hosting 'The Triwizard Tournament',\n
            a magical tournament between three well-known schools of magic : Hogwarts,\n
            Beauxbatons and Durmstrang. The contestants have to be above the age of 17,\n
            and are chosen by a magical object called Goblet of Fire.\n
            On the night of selection, however,\n
            the Goblet spews out four names instead of the usual three,\n
            with Harry unwittingly being selected as the Fourth Champion.\n
            Since the magic cannot be reversed,\n
            Harry is forced to go with it and brave three exceedingly difficult tasks."</item>
        <item>"After stealing a mysterious orb in the far reaches of outer space,\n
            Peter Quill from Earth is now the main target of a manhunt\n
            led by the villain known as Ronan the Accuser.\n
            To help fight Ronan and his team and save the galaxy from his power,\n
            Quill creates a team of space heroes known as the "Guardians of the Galaxy" to save the galaxy."</item>
        <item>"In a brand new Jumanji adventure, four high school kids discover an old video game console\n
            and are drawn into the game's jungle setting,\n
            literally becoming the adult avatars they chose.\n
            What they discover is that you don't just play Jumanji - you must survive it.\n
            To beat the game and return to the real world,\n
            they'll have to go on the most dangerous adventure of their lives,\n
            discover what Alan Parrish left 20 years ago, and change the way they think about themselves -\n
            or they'll be stuck in the game forever,\n
            to be played by others without break."</item>
        <item>"After the Baudelaire parents die in a terrible fire,\n
            the Baudelaire orphans search for their families secrets and get them\n
            and their fortune away from the terrible grasp of the sinister Count Olaf\n
            as he moves with them between different guardians in disguise."</item>
        <item>"The LEGO Movie is a 3D animated film which follows lead character,\n
            Emmet a completely ordinary LEGO mini-figure who is identified as the most "extraordinary person"\n
            and the key to saving the Lego universe.\n
            Emmet and his friends go on an epic journey to stop the evil tyrant, Lord Business."</item>
        <item>"This is the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson,\n
            who after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers,\n
            adopts the alter ego Deadpool.\n
            Armed with his new abilities and a dark,twisted sense of humor,\n
            Deadpool hunts down the man who nearly destroyed his life."</item>
        <item>"Marty McFly, a typical American teenager of the Eighties,\n
            is accidentally sent back to 1955 in a plutonium-powered DeLorean "time machine"\n
            invented by a slightly mad scientist.\n
            During his often hysterical, always amazing trip back in time,\n
            Marty must make certain his teenage parents-to-be meet and fall in love\n
            - so he can get back to the future."</item>
        <item>"The Doctor, a Time Lord from the race whose home planet is Gallifrey,\n
            travels through time and space in his/her ship the TARDIS\n
            (an acronym for Time and Relative Dimension In Space)\n
            with numerous companions.\n
            From time to time he/she regenerates into a new form\n
            (which is how the series has been running since the departure of the original actor,\n
            William Hartnell, in 1966)."</item>
        <item>"In the year 2043, scavenger James Cole (Aaron Stanford) has been recruited\n
            by a team of "Project Splinter" scientists led by physicist Katarina Jones (Barbara Sukowa),\n
            to travel back in time to the year 2015,\n
            and stop the release of a deadly virus by the enigmatic organization known as the\n
            "Army of the 12 Monkeys". In Cole's original time-line,\n
            the virus caused a plague that resulted in the death of seven billion humans in the year 2017,\n
            and its on-going mutations will mean the eventual end of the human race.\n
            In the 2015 time-line, Cole will meet and enlist the help of brilliant virologist\n
            Dr. Cassandra "Cassie" Railly (Amanda Schull);\n
            the two are brought together because a recording mentioning Cole,\n
            that Cassie made after the viral outbreak,\n
            is uncovered by Jones in the future time-line,\n
            prompting her to select Cole for the mission.\n
            Cole will also encounter a seemingly unstable math genius named Jennifer Goines (Emily Hampshire),\n
            whose father Cole has been tasked to kill, Cassie's"</item>
        <item>"Two FBI agents, Fox Mulder and Dana Scully work in an unassigned detail of the bureau\n
            called the X-Files investigating cases dealing with unexplained paranormal phenomena.\n
            Mulder, a true believer, and Scully, a skeptic,\n
            perceive their cases from stand points of science and the paranormal."</item>
        <item>"The FBI teams up with a formerly-institutionalized scientist\n
            - who was performing experiments on the fringe of real science\n
            - and his son to investigate weird crimes that are seemingly\n
            part of a larger pattern, and may be connected with a global company called Massive Dynamic."</item>
        <item>"Bob Parr (A.K.A. Mr. Incredible), and his wife Helen (A.K.A. Elastigirl),\n
            are the world's greatest famous crime-fighting superheroes in Metroville.\n
            Always saving lives and battling evil on a daily basis.\n
            But fifteen years later, they have been forced to adopt civilian identities\n
            and retreat to the suburbs where they have no choice but to\n
            retire as superheroes to live a "normal life" with their three children Violet,\n
            Dash and Jack-Jack (who were secretly born with superpowers).\n
            Itching to get back into action, Bob gets his chance when a mysterious\n
            communication summons him to a remote island for a top secret assignment.\n
            He soon discovers that it will take a super family effort to rescue the world\n
            from total destruction."</item>
        <item>"An animated series on adult-swim about the infinite adventures of Rick,\n
            a genius alcoholic and careless scientist,\n
            with his grandson Morty, a 14 year-old anxious boy who is not so smart.\n
            Together, they explore the infinite universes;\n
            causing mayhem and running into trouble."</item>
        <item>"When a devastating event befalls the city of San Fransokyo\n
            and catapults Hiro into the midst of danger,\n
            he turns to Baymax and his close friends adrenaline junkie Go Go Tomago,\n
            neatnik Wasabi, chemistry whiz Honey Lemon and fanboy Fred.\n
            Determined to uncover the mystery,\n
            Hiro transforms his friends into a band of high-tech heroes called "Big Hero 6."</item>
        <item>"Fearless optimist Anna teams up with rugged mountain man Kristoff and his loyal reindeer Sven\n
            and sets off on an epic journey to find her sister Elsa,\n
            whose icy powers have trapped the kingdom of Arendelle in eternal winter.\n
            Encountering Everest-like conditions,\n
            mystical trolls and a hilarious snowman named Olaf,\n
            Anna and Kristoff battle the elements in a race to save the kingdom.\n
            From the outside Elsa looks poised,\n
            regal and reserved, but in reality she lives in fear\n
            as she wrestles with a mighty secret: she was born with the power to create ice and snow.\n
            It's a beautiful ability, but also extremely dangerous.\n
            Haunted by the moment her magic nearly killed her younger sister Anna,\n
            Elsa has isolated herself, spending every waking minute trying\n
            to suppress her growing powers. Her mounting emotions trigger the magic,\n
            accidentally setting off an eternal winter that she can't stop.\n
            She fears she's becoming a monster and that no one,\n
            not even her sister, can help her. "</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>